freestreams.com 2016-10-18

# Privacy PolicyAgreementlast updatedFebruary23, 2015This is the Privacy Policy fordelPlaya Media, Inc.(“delPlaya Media”)that governsusage ofthe websiteslocated atwww.delPlayaMedia.com,www.AuthorizedStream.com,www.FreeStreams.com,www.FullviewPlayer.com, andwww.LyricFox.com(the “Websites”),theFreeStreamsmobile apps (the“Apps”),and any media application using thedelPlaya MediaService (as defined in the Terms of Use).Your Acceptance of this Privacy PolicyBy using theWebsites, Apps or delPlaya MediaService, including, without limitation, responding tooffers, exchanging information about your personal preferences, and continuing to receive informationfromdelPlaya Media, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and youexpressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information as described herein. ThisPrivacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Usefound at:http://www.freestreams.com/docs/termsofuse.pdfwhich is incorporated herein by this reference.Information We CollectIf you choose to share your personal information with us we will collect and retain information that maypersonally identify you (such as your name, location, mobile device identifier, physical address,telephone number, email address, billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked tosuch information).If you decide not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to use certain features oftheWebsites, Apps or delPlaya MediaService or other services.Even if you choose not to share your personal information, we may automatically collect non-personalinformation, including, but not limited to, IP (internet protocol) address, location, ISP (internet serviceprovider), the Web browser used to visit theWebsites, Apps ordelPlaya MediaService, length and timeof visit, the pages visited, a unique mobile device identifier and other usage datadelPlaya Mediamaycollect from time to time.We use "cookies" (small files placed on your computer to help optimize performance), single pixel GIFimage files (also called “Pixels” or "Web beacons"), Web server log analysis and other similartechnologies, and other tracking technology (such as Flash Persistent Storage) that help us manage andtrack your interaction with theWebsites, Apps and delPlaya MediaService. We may share suchinformation with third parties. We track the music played through thedelPlaya MediaService and report

Privacy Policy Agreement
last updated February 23, 2015
This is the Privacy Policy for delPlaya Media, Inc. (“delPlaya Media”) that governs usage of the websites
located at www.delPlayaMedia.com, www.AuthorizedStream.com, www.FreeStreams.com,
www.FullviewPlayer.com, and www.LyricFox.com (the “Websites”), the FreeStreams mobile apps (the
“Apps”), and any media application using the delPlaya Media Service (as defined in the Terms of Use).
Your Acceptance of this Privacy Policy
By using the Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media Service, including, without limitation, responding to
offers, exchanging information about your personal preferences, and continuing to receive information
from delPlaya Media, you agree to accept the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and you
expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information as described herein. This
Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Use found at:
http://www.freestreams.com/docs/termsofuse.pdf which is incorporated herein by this reference.
Information We Collect
If you choose to share your personal information with us we will collect and retain information that may
personally identify you (such as your name, location, mobile device identifier, physical address,
telephone number, email address, billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to
such information).
If you decide not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to use certain features of
the Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media Service or other services.
Even if you choose not to share your personal information, we may automatically collect non-personal
information, including, but not limited to, IP (internet protocol) address, location, ISP (internet service
provider), the Web browser used to visit the Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media Service, length and time
of visit, the pages visited, a unique mobile device identifier and other usage data delPlaya Media may
collect from time to time.
We use "cookies" (small files placed on your computer to help optimize performance), single pixel GIF
image files (also called “Pixels” or "Web beacons"), Web server log analysis and other similar
technologies, and other tracking technology (such as Flash Persistent Storage) that help us manage and
track your interaction with the Websites, Apps and delPlaya Media Service. We may share such
information with third parties. We track the music played through the delPlaya Media Service and report

it to our third party partners in the aggregate in order to meet their obligation to report and pay
copyright owners and for other lawful uses, including analytics and marketing undertaken by those third
parties. These reports do not contain personally-identifiable information.
We work with third party online advertising networks to deliver advertising on the Websites, Apps and
delPlaya Media Service. Such third parties may utilize cookies or other tracking and targeting
technologies. We are not responsible for information collected by third party advertisers in this manner,
nor for the collection or use of information by other sites to which the Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media
Service is linked.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers, ad networks, and
websites for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain
practices. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with us is maintained and
dealt with by us in accordance with this privacy policy. When you access the Websites, Apps or delPlaya
Media Service through a service partner, we may add your email address or other personalized
information, so that we can identify which of our service partners or other sign-in pages to send to you
when you log on.
We may also collect information about the devices you use to access the Websites, Apps or delPlaya
Media Service. This information may include your IP address, browser type, and other software or
hardware information. We also may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other
transactional information for that device.
Information We Receive From Third Parties
We may receive information about you from third parties and store it in our databases with personally
identifiable information that you provide to us. These third parties may include advertisers that make
features available through the Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media Service, access partners, and
marketing companies that create or sell other marketing data. delPlaya Media is only responsible for
abiding by its own privacy policy and will assume no liability if a business partner or other entity collects,
uses or shares any information about you in violation of its own privacy policy or applicable law.
Use of Information
We use your personal information and non-personal information to provide you with services, to notify
you of new products or services, and communicate with you. We also use the information that we
collect for the following purposes:
         • To customize and personalize the advertising and the content you see and hear.

         • To enhance the user experience in our network of websites and broadcasts. We use tracking
         information to enhance our offering.
         • To fulfill your requests to receive information or services and permit you to interact with the
         Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media Service.
         • To send you alerts on developments and features that may be of interest.
Consent to Sharing Information
We may rent, sell, and share your personal information and non-personal information with our network
partners and third-party affiliates for the purposes of direct mail, email marketing, mobile marketing,
and telemarketing. Additionally, we may share such personal information with the broadcaster to whose
station you use.
By providing personal information to us you agree:
         • all information you have provided is true and correct to the best of your knowledge;
         • you are establishing a business relationship with delPlaya Media and with its advertising and
         marketing partners; and
         • you are requesting and expressly consenting to be contacted via telephone (whether wireless
         or wired), including by live or prerecorded, calls using an automated dialing system, email,
         and/or mail by us, our network partners, and third-party affiliates and marketing partners
         regardless of whether your telephone number is on any Do Not Call list(s)
         • From time to time, we may establish a business relationship with other businesses and third
         party marketing partners whom we believe trustworthy and who have confirmed that their
         privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract
         with Service Providers and third-party marketing partners to provide certain services, such as
         hosting and maintenance, customer relationship management, data storage and management,
         and direct marketing campaigns. We provide our Service Providers and/or third-party marketing
         partners with the information necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf. Each
         Service Provider and/or third-party marketing partner must agree to use reasonable security
         procedures and practices, appropriate to the nature of the information involved, in order to
         protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
We may work with third-party marketing and advertising companies ("Ad Networks"). These companies
may collect and use information about your use of the Websites, Apps and delPlaya Media Service in
order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.
Advertisements may be shown via the Websites, Apps and delPlaya Media Service, or third-party sites.
These companies may use cookies or other tracking technologies. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any
use of information that an Ad Network may collect from you. It also does not cover any information that

you may choose to provide to an Ad Network or to an advertiser whose goods or services are advertised
through the Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media Service. For such information, you are subject to the
terms of the Ad Networks’ privacy policy. We may share personal information and non-personal
information with businesses controlling, controlled by, or under common control with delPlaya Media. If
delPlaya Media is merged, acquired, or sold, or in the event of a transfer of some or all of our assets, we
may disclose or transfer personal information and non-personal information in connection with such
transaction. We shall also cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties
to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose personal information and non-personal
information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if, in our discretion,
we believe it is necessary or appropriate in order to respond to legal requests (including court orders
and subpoenas), to protect the safety, property or rights of delPlaya Media or of any third party, to
prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we receive
personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records
once we learn of it.
External Links
The Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media Service may contain links to other sites, or allow others to send
you such links. A link to a third party's site does not mean that we endorse it or that we are affiliated
with it. We do not exercise control over third-party sites. You access such third-party sites or content at
your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a third- party site before providing any
information to the site.
Opting Out
delPlaya Media uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These
companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number)
about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services
of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices
about not having this information used by these companies, go to:
http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, you may write to
us at:
                  delPlaya Media, Inc.,
                  Attn: Data Privacy
                  P.O. Box 50747

                  Montecito, CA 93150
Please provide complete information to facilitate your request, as well as your complete contact
information.
Privacy Policy Changes
From time to time, we may change this Privacy Policy. If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will
inform you by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Websites, Apps and delPlaya Media Service.
Those changes will go into effect on the revision date shown in the revised Privacy Policy. Your
continued use of the Websites, Apps or delPlaya Media Service constitutes your consent to be bound by
the revised Privacy Policy.
Your California Privacy Rights
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers who are California residents to request certain
information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties'
direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to:
        delPlaya Media, Inc.,
        Attn: Data Privacy
        P.O. Box 50747
        Montecito, CA 93150
